{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Built-In Furniture Makers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46370/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46370,"taskName":"Built-In Furniture - Construct","taskDescription":"Construct Built-In Furniture","xmTaskDescriptor":"Built-In Furniture Makers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5117,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"built-in bedroom shelves master office","textMessagingName":"Built-In Furn.","rolloverLongDesc":"Constructs Built-In Furniture from scratch to precisely fit the space \u0026 the customer's needs, both functional \u0026 aesthetic. Emphasis is on high quality \u0026 custom work, not low price.","rolloverShortDesc":"Skilled carpenter for Built-In Furniture.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Construct Built-In Furniture.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Built-In Cabinets \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Built-In Shelves","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Built-In Furniture","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Built-In Furniture - Construct","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Built-In Furniture Project","urlName":"Built-In-Furniture-Construct","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Built-In Cabinet \u0026 Shelf Makers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"built-in,bedroom,shelves,master,office,bookcase,custom,furniture,build, bookshelfs, book, bookshelves","emcCategoryOid":-12009,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1295,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46370/":{"taskOID":46370,"originalTaskOID":46370,"setID":1295,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6324,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Built-In","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of Built-In furniture would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20285,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bookshelves","answerDisplayText":"Bookshelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20286,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom storage","answerDisplayText":"Custom storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20287,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Seating","answerDisplayText":"Seating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20432,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall Unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall Unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6325,"questionDisplayText":"Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to install the Built-In?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20290,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20291,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20292,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20293,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20294,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Location","answerDisplayText":"Other Location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20295,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6326,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material do you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Oak","answerDisplayText":"Oak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20297,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Paint grade","answerDisplayText":"Paint grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20298,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maple","answerDisplayText":"Maple","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20299,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cherry","answerDisplayText":"Cherry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20300,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20301,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20302,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6327,"questionDisplayText":"Features Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20303,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Adjustable shelves","answerDisplayText":"Adjustable shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lazy Susan","answerDisplayText":"Lazy Susan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eating counter","answerDisplayText":"Eating counter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20307,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pull-out shelves","answerDisplayText":"Pull-out shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20308,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Desk/computer area","answerDisplayText":"Desk/computer area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20309,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pantry cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Pantry cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20311,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6324,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Built-In","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of Built-In furniture would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20285,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bookshelves","answerDisplayText":"Bookshelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20286,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom storage","answerDisplayText":"Custom storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20287,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Seating","answerDisplayText":"Seating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20432,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall Unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall Unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20285,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bookshelves","answerDisplayText":"Bookshelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20286,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom storage","answerDisplayText":"Custom storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20287,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Seating","answerDisplayText":"Seating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20432,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall Unit","answerDisplayText":"Wall Unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6325,"questionDisplayText":"Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to install the Built-In?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20290,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20291,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20292,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20293,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20294,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Location","answerDisplayText":"Other Location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20295,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20290,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20291,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20292,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20293,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entertainment center","answerDisplayText":"Entertainment center","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20294,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Location","answerDisplayText":"Other Location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20295,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6326,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material do you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Oak","answerDisplayText":"Oak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20297,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Paint grade","answerDisplayText":"Paint grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20298,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maple","answerDisplayText":"Maple","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20299,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cherry","answerDisplayText":"Cherry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20300,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20301,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20302,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Oak","answerDisplayText":"Oak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20297,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Paint grade","answerDisplayText":"Paint grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20298,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maple","answerDisplayText":"Maple","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20299,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cherry","answerDisplayText":"Cherry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20300,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20301,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20302,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6327,"questionDisplayText":"Features Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20303,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Adjustable shelves","answerDisplayText":"Adjustable shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lazy Susan","answerDisplayText":"Lazy Susan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eating counter","answerDisplayText":"Eating counter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20307,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pull-out shelves","answerDisplayText":"Pull-out shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20308,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Desk/computer area","answerDisplayText":"Desk/computer area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20309,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pantry cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Pantry cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20311,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20303,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Adjustable shelves","answerDisplayText":"Adjustable shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lazy Susan","answerDisplayText":"Lazy Susan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eating counter","answerDisplayText":"Eating counter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20307,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pull-out shelves","answerDisplayText":"Pull-out shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20308,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Desk/computer area","answerDisplayText":"Desk/computer area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20309,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pantry cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Pantry cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20311,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}